<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="pine_permission_system_alert_window_text">Floating window permission required to display floating content</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_system_alert_window_description">This permission is used to display floating windows on top of other apps, such as mini windows, bubble tips, etc.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_camera_text">Camera permission required to use related features</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_camera_description">This permission is used for features that require the camera, such as taking photos, scanning QR codes, etc.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_coarse_location_text">Location permission required to obtain approximate geographic location</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_coarse_location_description">This permission is used for network-based location services, such as querying nearby content.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_fine_location_text">Precise location permission required to provide location services</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_fine_location_description">This permission is used for features that require precise positioning, such as maps, navigation, etc.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_foreground_service_location_text">Foreground location service permission required to continuously obtain location</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_foreground_service_location_description">This permission allows the app to continuously obtain your location information while running in the background, used for navigation, exercise tracking, and other features.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_read_external_storage_text">Read storage permission required to access files</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_read_external_storage_description">This permission is used to read media content such as photos and files on the device.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_audio_text">Access audio permission required to browse media content</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_audio_description">This permission is used to read audio files on the device.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_images_text">Read storage permission required to access photos</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_images_description">This permission is used to read media content such as photos and files on the device.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_video_text">Access video permission required to browse media content</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_read_media_video_description">This permission is used to read video files on the device.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_record_audio_text">Microphone permission required for recording</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_record_audio_description">This permission is used for features that require the microphone, such as voice input, recording, etc.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_write_external_storage_text">Storage permission required to save files</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_write_external_storage_description">This permission is used to save content such as photos and files to the device.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_activity_recognition_text">Activity recognition permission required for step counting</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_activity_recognition_description">This permission is used to read device motion sensor data, count your daily steps, track exercise distance, and other health information.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_background_location_text">Background location permission required to access location when the app is not in use</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_background_location_description">This permission allows the app to obtain your location even when running in the background or when the screen is off, used for features such as continuous activity tracking, safety monitoring, or location-based automation.</string>

    <string name="pine_permission_post_notifications_text">Notification permission required to display foreground service notifications</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_post_notifications_description">This permission allows the app to show notifications, which are required for foreground services such as background location tracking and ongoing activity updates.</string>


    <string name="pine_permission_title">Permission Request</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_redirect_to_setting">Go to app settings to authorize</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_auth_now">Authorize Now</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_auth_later">Later</string>
    <string name="pine_permission_descritpion">After authorization, you can enjoy a more complete functional experience.</string>



</resources>